russianforfree.com 2019-12-14

# Privacy policy - Learn Russian for Free

## User agreement

russianforfree.com (the "Service") is accessible worldwide to anyone with Internet access. Access to and use of the Service is subject to the terms and conditions of this User Agreement and Copyright Notice and all applicable laws and regulations, including laws and regulations governing copyright and trademark. BY ACCESSING THE SERVICE, YOU ACCEPT, WITHOUT LIMITATION OR QUALIFICATION, ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS IN THIS USER AGREEMENT. russianforfree.com and its affiliates reserve the right to change these terms and conditions at any time. The changes will appear on this screen. By using the Service, you agree in advance to accept any changes.

In compliance the Data Protection Law 34/2002, we provide here our details:

José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.)  
Leoncio Suárez 11 Bajo D  
33209 Gijón, Asturias  
ES-53526575-D  
Tlf. +34 984 833 756  

* * *

## Cookie Policy

### What Are Cookies

As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or 'break' certain elements of the sites functionality.

### How We Use Cookies

We use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.

### The Cookies We Set

If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out however in some cases they may remain afterwards to remember your site preferences when logged out.

We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in.

This site offers newsletter or email subscription services and cookies may be used to remember if you are already registered and whether to show certain notifications which might only be valid to subscribed/unsubscribed users.

This site offers e-commerce or payment facilities and some cookies are essential to ensure that your order is remembered between pages so that we can process it properly.

When you submit data to through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment forms cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence.

In order to provide you with a great experience on this site we provide the functionality to set your preferences for how this site runs when you use it. In order to remember your preferences we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is affected by your preferences.

### Third Party Cookies

In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.

### GOOGLE AND GOOGLE ANALYTICS COOKIES

Google Analytics is a simple, easy-to-use tool that helps website owners measure how users interact with website content. As a user navigates between web pages, Google Analytics provides website owners JavaScript tags (libraries) to record information about the page a user has seen, for example the URL of the page. The Google Analytics JavaScript libraries use HTTP Cookies to "remember" what a user has done on previous pages / interactions with the website.

Names of the cookies:

_utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmv  
_utmz  

**Further information about Google**

Here you will find complete information about Google, and their cookies and privacy policies:

  * These [Google Analytics security and privacy principles](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en) summarize the steps Google takes to keep user's data protected
  * [How Google uses data](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/) when you visit our website
  * To provide website visitors the ability to prevent their data from being used by Google Analytics, Googles has developed this [Google Analytics opt-out browser](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

Important: Google Analytics does not store any personal information about your website users. Read the Google Analytics privacy document for more details. Google Analytics supports two JavaScript libraries (tags) for measuring website usage: analytics.js and ga.js. The following sections describe how each use cookies.

### analytics.js – Cookie Usage

The analytics.js JavaScript library is part of Universal Analytics and uses first-party cookies to:

Distinguish unique users  
Throttle the request rate  
By default, this library sets cookies on the top level domain, excluding the leading dot, and sets the cookie path to the root level (/).

Note: The analytics.js library does not require setting cookies to transmit data to Google Analytics.

This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content. For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.

### FACEBOOK COOKIES

Facebook does not use cookies to create a profile of your browsing behavior on third-party sites or to show you ads, although it may use anonymous or aggregate data to improve ads generally. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases, this may impact your ability to use Facebook. For more information, visit [Facebook’s Cookie Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy/cookies/)

### TWITTER COOKIES

Twitter may use cookies to better understand how you interact with their services, to monitor aggregate usage by Twitter users and web traffic routing to their services. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases, this may impact your ability to use Twitter. For more information, visit [Twitter’s Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy)

### YOUTUBE AND GOOGLE COOKIES

The following YouTube and Google features may be integrated into our website and may store cookies from YouTube or Google: YouTube Video Player (plays YouTube videos on our website)

Login to your YouTube account (allows users to log into their YouTube account and interact them)  
Google + 1 button (allows users to tag an item in their Google+ account)  
Goole Log in (allows users to log into their Google account and interact with our website through that account).  
For more information, visit [Google's privacy policy (also valid for Youtube)](https://www.google.es/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

### Disabling Cookies

You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of the this site. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.

* * *

## Intellectual Property

The source code , graphic design , images , animations , software , texts , databases , as well as the information and contents included in the domain russianforfree.com are property of José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) or its suppliers. None of it may be reproduced or published by any means without the prior written permission of José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) .

Users may solely and exclusively use the material which appears on this website for their personal and private use. It is forbidden to use it for commercial purposes or to engage in activities contrary to law.

* * *

## Conditions of use of the website russianforfree.com

The use of the website implies full and unreserved acceptance of each and every one of the points included in this Legal Notice from the very moment when the user accesses the website. Consequently, the user must carefully read this Legal Notice.  
1\. José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) may modify or update, without notice, the information contained in the website, as well as its layout, presentation and access conditions.  
2\. All information, pictures and data appearing on this website may be modified without notice according to the will of José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.).  
3\. The User agrees to use the website in accordance with the law and this Privacy Policy as well as morality and generally accepted good practices and public order.  
4\. José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) ensures that all content and services offered on russianforfree.com respect the principle of dignity, the principle of non - discrimination based on race, sex , religion , nationality , disability or any other personal or social circumstance as well as the principle of protection of youth and childhood.  
5\. José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) is committed through this means NOT TO ENGAGE IN MISLEADING ADVERTISING. This does not include formal or numeric errors which may be found throughout the content of the various sections of the website. russianforfree.com will strive to correct any error as soon as we detect them.  
6\. José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) will NOT SEND ADVERTISING OR CORRESPONDENCE WITHOUT IDENTIFYING IT AS SUCH, in accordance with the provisions of Law 34/2002 of Services of the Information Society and Electronic Commerce.  
It will not be considered as advertising information sent to users with the intention of maintaining the existing contractual relationship between client and José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) and the performance of tasks of information and other activities of the service that the client could contract with the company. In some cases, we will contact our customers and users to inform them about learning resources that we provide for the study of Spanish.  
7\. The access to this website and the use of the information contained there is the sole responsibility of the user. J.A.S.T. is not responsible for any consequence or damage that may arise from such access or use of information. J.A.S.T. is not responsible for any possible security errors that may occur or for any damage caused to the user's computer system (hardware and software), or to the files or documents stored as the result of the presence of virus in the computer used to connect to the services and web content, or because of a malfunction of the browser or the use of non-updated versions.  
8\. José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) and the user will resolve any dispute, expressly waiving any other jurisdiction, at the courts of the city of Gijón (Spain).

* * *

## Privacy Policy. Data protection

Data processing will be done in compliance with the Data Protection Law 15/1999 , of December 13 , Protection of Personal Data , which is intended to ensure and protect the processing of personal data , public freedom and fundamental rights of individuals, and especially their honor and personal and family privacy. José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) informs all users of russianforfree.com about this policy to protect personal data, so that users can, with total freedom, to decide whether to provide the information which might be required in connection with the subscription or registration on any of José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) services offered through its website.

José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) reserves the right to modify these terms in order to adapt to legislative changes or industry practices, in which case it shall inform in advance by notice on this page.

The personal data which you provide when completing the Application Form or register on any of our services that require registration or subscription, will be subject to the Data Protection Law. Data will be part of the José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.) MANAGEMENT files, in order to maintain the contractual relationships, if any, and for administrative purposes and tasks related to expansion and improvement of our services and process, including sending information and advertising about offers, promotions and recommendations, and to make statistics and analysis of market trends and surveys, that the user is not in any way obliged to answer.

Except in areas where otherwise indicated, the answers to questions about your data is voluntary, but the lack of response to the same quality implies a decline, or inability to provide the service unless otherwise indicated.

Also note that you have the possibility of exercising rights of access, rectification , cancellation and opposition of you personal data , with the File Manager:

José A. Santiago Tomás (J.A.S.T.)  
Leoncio Suárez 11 Bajo D  
33209 Gijón, Asturias  
ES-53526575-D  
Tlf. +34 984 833 756
